Patty Fresonke

915 2nd Street South Moorhead, MN 56560 218.234.7598 pattyfresonke@gmail.com

Summary

More than eight years of experience in web development, including Drupal and Escenic CUE. Over four years of experience in a computer help desk setting providing assistance to students, faculty, clients, and employees.

Able to learn new concepts quickly, work with others and alone, and multitask projects.

Experience

Software Engineer

Forum Communications Company | Fargo, ND | 2011 - Present

Develop and maintain code in both front-end design and back-end aspects of FCC websites.

Work with fellow team members to complete tasks and meet deadlines.

Provide support for internal employees and end-users and solve issues in a timely manner.

IT Support Technician

Arvig Communication Systems | Perham, MN | March 2011 - June 2011

Run diagnostics and provide troubleshooting both in person and remotely.

Maintain and update hardware and software on company computers.

Communicate processes and solutions with employees and users.

Computer Help Center

Minnesota State Community and Technical College | Detroit Lakes, MN | 2007 - 2011

Troubleshoot problems; such as viruses, hardware and software issues, logging into systems.

Upgrade, replace, and install hardware components in laptops and desktops.

Create training and informational presentations as well as instructional documents.

Recreational Coach

Minnesota Flyers Gymnastics | Detroit Lakes, MN | 2007 - 2011

Develop gymnastics and motor skills while helping build confidence and life skills.

Technical Skills

Proficient in HTML, CSS/SCSS/Sass, PHP, JavaScript, Git, Twig templates, and Agile workflow.

Able to work resourcefully with Atomic Design, AngularJS, Google CSE, and React.

Familiar with databases and MySQL.

Experience using Adobe Creative Suite and Microsoft Office.

Knowledge and experience developing cross browser compatible, responsive websites.

Education

Udacity

Nanodegree, Front-End Web Development

Oct 2018

Minnesota State Community and Technical College (M|State) | Detroit Lakes, MN

Associate of Applied Science, Web Development May 2011 Associate of Applied Science, Computer & Network Technology May 2011 May 2009

Associate of Applied Science, Computer Network Security

Notable Accomplishments Grow with Google Developer Scholarship Recipient (Phase 1 & 2 of Udacity partnership)

Member and secretary of M|State-Detroit Lakes Student Senate

Charter member and secretary of the Beta Pi Si chapter of the Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society

Three-time member of the M|State Collegiate Cyber Defense Team

Instructor for Community Education on basic technology skills and social media concepts